[{"answer": " So, Molly, do you want to watch the Olympics next week", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Its the summer Olympics, right", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 13, "question": " So, Molly, do you want to watch the Olympics next week", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Yeah.  Its August.  The Winter Olympics arent on till February", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Its the summer Olympics, right", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " I think I like the Winter Olympics better.  I like to watch the skiing and the ice", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Yeah.  Its August.  The Winter Olympics arent on till February", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " I like those sports too.    But, the Summer Olympics have a lot of good sports t", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 19, "question": " I think I like the Winter Olympics better.  I like to watch the skiing and the ice", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": " I like those sports too.    But, the Summer Olympics have a lot of good sports t", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Yeah.  In fact, there are almost three times as many summer sports as winte", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Which do you think we should watch", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Yeah.  In fact, there are almost three times as many summer sports as winte", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Well, theres running, swimming, basketball, gymnastics, volleyball, tenni", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Which do you think we should watch", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Oh!  I forgot about gymnastics.  I love watching that", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Well, theres running, swimming, basketball, gymnastics, volleyball, tenni", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " It is a very exciting sport to watch.  I cant imagine how those girls can do all o", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Oh!  I forgot about gymnastics.  I love watching that", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " I know.  Its so cool.  Remember when I used to want to be a gymnast", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 38, "question": " It is a very exciting sport to watch.  I cant imagine how those girls can do all o", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Yeah.  You stuck with your classes for a while.  But, then you gave it up", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 39, "question": " I know.  Its so cool.  Remember when I used to want to be a gymnast", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Yeah.  It was just too hard.  Im not cut out for that kind of thing", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Yeah.  You stuck with your classes for a while.  But, then you gave it up", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Well, you could always give it another try.  Its not too late you know", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Yeah.  It was just too hard.  Im not cut out for that kind of thing", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Well see", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Well, you could always give it another try.  Its not too late you know", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Well see", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " So, Mom, have the Olympic sports always been the same", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 47, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 48, "question": " So, Mom, have the Olympic sports always been the same", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " The Olympics started a long time ago, right?  Have the same sports always bee", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 49, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " You know, I was reading about that in the paper.  The Olympics started in 1896", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 53, "question": " The Olympics started a long time ago, right?  Have the same sports always bee", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Thats a long time ago", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 54, "question": " You know, I was reading about that in the paper.  The Olympics started in 1896", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " I know.  The sports have changed since then, too.  Its funny.  I was reading tha", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Thats a long time ago", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Tug-of-war?  Really", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 59, "question": " I know.  The sports have changed since then, too.  Its funny.  I was reading tha", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Yep.  Back in the early 1900s", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Tug-of-war?  Really", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " I would never think of that as a professional sport", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Yep.  Back in the early 1900s", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": "   I also read that people are trying to get things like ballroom dancing and vide", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 62, "question": " I would never think of that as a professional sport", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Video games?  Theres no physical skill needed for that.  You cant call that ", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 66, "question": "   I also read that people are trying to get things like ballroom dancing and vide", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " I know.  I dont think theres even a chance that it will become an Olympic sport", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Video games?  Theres no physical skill needed for that.  You cant call that ", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Crazy.  But, I guess people wouldnt consider tug-of-war a sport today either", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 77, "question": " I know.  I dont think theres even a chance that it will become an Olympic sport", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Thats right.  Times change and so do peoples ideas about sports.  You neve", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Crazy.  But, I guess people wouldnt consider tug-of-war a sport today either", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " That would probably make a lot of the boys at my school happy", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Thats right.  Times change and so do peoples ideas about sports.  You neve", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " OK.  Were almost home.  Lets have dinner and then take a look at the schedul", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 83, "question": " That would probably make a lot of the boys at my school happy", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " OK.  Sounds good", "docId": "08-09", "aSentId": 87, "question": " OK.  Were almost home.  Lets have dinner and then take a look at the schedul", "qSentId": 86}]
